Good morning. I just want to let you all know that views from Amanda Land will be starting
at 10 a.m. Eastern at YouTube Amanda Seals TV. I also want to let you all know that IG is effing
with me. They have made it so that I can't see any of my comments on any of my posts.
And this means that they are feeling morning, Dickie. This means that they feel that I am
speaking truths that they do not want out there. So if you're leaving comments, etc., just know that
I can't see you. This is a good time to subscribe to my YouTube Amanda Seals TV. And if you have $5
to spare every month, this is a great time to join my Patreon to support the work that I'm doing. It
is my sole source of income. I shouldn't have said that because now they're going to come from my
Patreon. Nonetheless, that is what's going on. So I wanted to let you all know that and hope that you
will come over to YouTube Amanda Seals TV today. Click the live tab and join us at Views for
Amanda Land 10 a.m. Eastern for what is going to be an incredibly lively conversation per usual.
We'll be joined by Logan Lurice, a.k.a. Focus on Infinity. We're going to be talking about Zoron.
We're also going to talk about the continued attacks on the Sumut Flotilla. We're also going
to talk about apartheid in L.A. as we are talking about how the Supreme Court has now made, has
literally ruled that profiling is completely okay. And what are the continued, I do have
a backup account. And what are the continued next steps that happen after that? Later on in
the show, I am going to be talking about the RICO charges that were dismissed against the Cop City
protesters in Atlanta. This is in our Blackie Rick News segment. Also going to be talking about the
actors who have signed on to boycott Israel, including myself. And we're going to talk about
that Ayo Edibari interview that took place in Italy that was banonkers. Banonkers. Our Level Us Up
guest this morning is Laura Chung, who is a psychic astrologist who's also my homegirl. She is a Korean
queen. And she will be joining us to give us the latest and greatest on what the stars are saying
about where we are and where we're going. And I will tell you, and I will always say this, is that
the greatest astrology reading I have ever had in my life has come from Laura Chung, I believe
greatly in her abilities and capabilities. So this is all going on today. And our critical thinking
exercise for this episode is going to be about why is there no working class rage? Where is the
working class rage? We're going to talk about it. We're going to get into what it is, why that is the
case. And as usual, the goal is to get that brain cooking and moving. Some people have asked, why don't
I do this show in the evening? Because your brain is tired in the evening. I do it in the morning
because that's when you're up. That's when your brain is awake. That's when your brain is sharp.
And that's why we do Views for Amanda Land Wednesday mornings at 10 a.m. Eastern. So I will see you
10 a.m. Eastern at YouTube, Amanda Seals TV. Mwah!